[{"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "6"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "1"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [5], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "7"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "1"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [6], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "8"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "1"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [7], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "1"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [8], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "1"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [9], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "6"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "2"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "7"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "2"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [5], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "8"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "2"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [6], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "2"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [7], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "2"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [8], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "6"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "3"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [3], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "7"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "3"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "8"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "3"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [5], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "3"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [6], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "3"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [7], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "6"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "4"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "7"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "4"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [3], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "8"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "4"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "4"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [5], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "4"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [6], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "6"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "5"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "7"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "5"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "8"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "5"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [3], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "5"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "5"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [5], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "7"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "6"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "8"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "6"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "6"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [3], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "6"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "8"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "7"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "7"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "7"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [3], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "8"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "8"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "9"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-12-01"}]